<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- edited with XMLSpy v2020 (x64) (http://www.altova.com) by Andrew Auseon (Private) -->
<Root>
	<Entry>
		<zType>TEXT_EVENTSTORY_STUDY_ASTRONOMY_ARCHETYPES</zType>
		<English><![CDATA[Now that {CHARACTER-0} has completed <masculine_CHARACTER-0>his<feminine>her<end> study of astronomy, how shall <masculine_CHARACTER-0>he<feminine>she<end> contribute to the court? 

What role best suits {CHARACTER-SHORT-0}? ]]></English>
	</Entry>
	<Entry>
		<zType>TEXT_EVENTSTORY_DEAR_PARENT_ASTRONOMY</zType>
		<English><![CDATA[We have received an update from your <masculine_CHARACTER-0>son<feminine>daughter<end> in training. <masculine_CHARACTER-0>He<feminine>She<end> wishes to study with high masters of astronomy, whose teachings are essential to inquisitive nature of humankind. However, this access comes at a price.

Shall we send the necessary funds to {CHARACTER-SHORT-0}?]]></English>
	</Entry>
	<Entry>
		<zType>TEXT_EVENTSTORY_TACTICS_TO_ASTRONOMY</zType>
		<English><![CDATA[We have heard reports that {CHARACTER-0} struggles with <masculine_CHARACTER-0>his<feminine>her<end> tactics training. Perhaps we should explore educating <masculine_CHARACTER-0>him<feminine>her<end> in astronomy instead.

What shall we do?]]></English>
	</Entry>
	<Entry>
		<zType>TEXT_EVENTSTORY_ASTRONOMY_TO_COMMERCE</zType>
		<English><![CDATA[News has reached us that your heir, {CHARACTER-SHORT-0}, ignores the lessons of <masculine_CHARACTER-0>his<feminine>her<end> astronomy masters. The court wishes to invest wisely in {CHARACTER-SHORT-0}, but perhaps astronomy is not <masculine_CHARACTER-0>his<feminine>her<end> calling.

How shall we proceed?]]></English>
	</Entry>
	<Entry>
		<zType>TEXT_EVENTSTORY_GRADUATION_STUDIES_COMPLETE_ASTRONOMY</zType>
		<English><![CDATA[{CHARACTER-SHORT-0}, the young heir, has returned from <masculine_CHARACTER-0>his<feminine>her<end> astronomy studies, but <masculine_CHARACTER-0>he<feminine>she<end> would like to retain a tutor for additional training.

What shall be the focus of <masculine_CHARACTER-0>his<feminine>her<end> continuing education?]]></English>
	</Entry>
	<Entry>
		<zType>TEXT_EVENTSTORY_STUDY_BEARDY_MAN</zType>
		<English><![CDATA[One day after studies have ended sooner, {CHARACTER-0} decided to roam through the city. <masculine_CHARACTER-0>He<feminine>She<end> stumbled towards this old beardy looking man sitting on the ground. Suddenly something was catching <masculine_CHARACTER-0>his<feminine>her<end> eyes.<br>
		It was a book from Plato, a rare examplare <masculine_CHARACTER-0>he<feminine>she<end> was always eager to set eyes on. {CHARACTER-0} directly notcied <masculine_CHARACTER-0>he<feminine>she<end> have the same interests.  They kept talking for a while until <masculine_CHARACTER-0>he<feminine>she<end> asked if <masculine_CHARACTER-0>he<feminine>she<end> can have a look at the book.<br>
		<masculine_CHARACTER-0>He<feminine>She<end> shared a recent presumption	<masculine_CHARACTER-0>he<feminine>she<end> made while watching the sun go down the other day. The sun went down very quikcly and {CHARACTER-0} noticed that <masculine_CHARACTER-0>he<feminine>she<end> did not even aks why this man looks so needy.<br>
		The mand replied that he is not here to seek pitty. Then he told you about how he has lost his wife and kinds and thi sbook is the only thing he could save from hus burnng home.
		
		
What did you take along at the end of the day?]]></English>
	</Entry>
</Root>
